Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
The show is squishing!
Punirunes. Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
Sometimes they're kachi-freezy and hard too!
These are some merry, adorable puni-pals.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Airune
Becomes a Babyrune♪
"Airune Becomes a Babyrune♪"
So adorable!
They're looking at pictures
from when Yuka was a baby.
You were so squishy back then.
Very squishy indeed!
Squishy!
It was a hard time...
but it was so much fun.
Remember Yuka's first word?
How could I forget? It was "mommy!"
Huh? Wasn't it "daddy?"
No, it was "mommy!"
It was "daddy!"
Nope. "Mommy!"
"Daddy!"
Not "daddy," "mommy!"
Puni-puni.
Aw, I want to squish a baby too!
Angelrune
This little one is Angelrune.
Its arrows bring luck to those they hit.
Huh, me?
But its aim isn't very good.
Airune?!
Babyrune
Huh?! Airune turned into a Babyrune!
So this is the squishiness of a baby!
It's so squishy!
So adorable!
Puni-puni-puni-puni-puni...!
What's the matter?
Oh, I see. You're hungry!
That calls for...
Let's Get Squ-ooking!
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the
squishsterious squishence...
Stir it up, knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading
so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Appuni pie, ready to serve!
Appuni Pie
Enjoy!
Airune, what's wrong?
Now that it's had its meal...
Oh, I see! You need the potty!
Hang in there, Airune!
Glad you're feeling better.
I wonder if its poop is squishy too...
Y-Yuka?
I was just kidding, obviously!
You didn't seem kidding.
You were so brave going
to the potty by yourself!
Airune?!
Oh? What's happening?
Huh?
Redrune
Redrune!
Punirunes grow when they're cared for.
Redrune's squishiness is just perfect too!
Yuka, come look at this!
Can't, I'm busy!
I baked a really cool bread! Hurry!
A really cool bread?
Airune, wait here!
Airune, I'm back!
What?!
Airune?!
Punirunes melt when they're lonely.
Airune? Airune!
Airune, I won't let you feel lonely again!
Good night, Airune!
Punirunes go to sleep at 8:00.
I have to go to school tomorrow.
But I don't want you to feel lonely!
Yuka.
Huh?
You're not the only one who
wants to take care of Airune.
We're here for it too.
Yeah!
Dad, Mom!
Goodbye!
Take care!
Puni-puni!
Since Yuka's desk is dirty...
they're cleaning it up by collecting dust
with their squishy bodies!
I'm home!
Oh, you cleaned up! Thank you!
Huh?!
You're all dirty...
Then let's give you a bath!
It's fun bathing you all together.
You burned up! Are you okay?
You're even squishier when you're clean!
Okay.
Airune!
This is it! This is Airune's squishiness!
But it was so fun squishing you
as a Babyrune too!
Angelrune?
Huh? Again?
But Angelrune's a bit different today!
Huh? What? Huh?!
The plan: the more, the likelier!
Huh?!
So adorable!
Puni-Pal Files!
Today, I'll tell you about...
Coolrune
Coolrune!
Coolrune is cool and stylish!
It's a great dancer too!
When everyone's in trouble,
it comes up with ideas and helps out!
But there's one more thing Coolrune is good at!
Time for the Puni-Pal Squestion!
What is it?
1. Cooking
2. Cleaning
3. Sitting
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
2. Cleaning!
It loves keeping tidy!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, what'cha laughing about?
Huh? You're making a school in Puniland?
That sounds like fun!
Next Time
Interesting... Language, math,
science, and social studies?
So you're doing all sorts of classes!
Next Time
But can you really pull it off?
Next time: "Puni School is In Session♪"
Puni School is
In Session♪
"Puni" in next time!